Andrew Before

dbefore@u.washington.edu

www.dbefore.com

(509) 389-1901

SUMMARY

GPA - 3.5

A student-athlete with strong programming skills primarily learned through Java. Full-Stack web development skills using HTML, CSS, JavaScript; React, Firebase, AJAX, Node, and Mongo. Team oriented and self-driven. Experienced working with a team and collaborating over mediums like Git.

SKILLS UX Programming Software

Prototyping HTML/CSS Photoshop
Research JavaScript Illustrator
Visual Design Java/C# After Effects
Wireframes SQL Unity3D

EDUCATION

University of Washington, Seattle WA

Informatics major graduating 2017

Relevant courses include: Programming, Data Structures & Algorithms, Information Architecture, Web Development, Design Thinking, Immersive Environment Design, Mobile App Design, and skills in the Adobe Suite.

EXPERIENCE

Atavus- Seattle, Washington 2016

Analyst – Worked with the marketing team with a focus on the website, search engine optimization, and web traffic analytics.

- Improved current search engine optimization
- Worked with a team on marketing strategy and analysis
- Wire framed and developed restructured website

Best In Class- Seattle, Washington 2015-2016

Graphic Designer – Took on several projects to create required Graphics. Worked on web and paper formats.

- Helped with User experience flow of website
- Acquired experience working with deadlines and working to fulfill specific requirements

Capstone- Seattle, Washington 2016-2017

https://Blockbusters.group

Produced a new dataset combining DarkWeb archive and Bitcoin Blockchain.

- Led project design, designing and creating a research video, promotional video, and capstone poster
- Created templates to be used with parser for scraping data
- Built Capstone research video, promotional video, and poster
- Researched dataset with thematic analysis and data visualizations

ACHIEVEMENTS

Division I Athlete - Football, University of Washington, 2013 – 2017 Nine Times Dean's List